Guide to the TV Tie-in Book Collection, 1945-1999
TV Tie-in Book Collection, 1945-1999
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Collection of TV tie-in books,1945-1999, 1945-1999
8001
1370 vol.
Books.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
1,370 TV tie-in paperbacks and hardbacks about American TV shows from the beginning of TV in the 1940's to the turn of the century.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
1,370 TV tie-in paperbacks and hardbacks about American TV shows from the beginning of TV in the 1940's to the turn of the century.
SUBJECTS
Subjects:
Television programs.; Television and literature.; Television and reading.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- A for Andromeda by Fred Hoyle and John Elliot Crest d773 ca. 1962 (1st 1964) (Box 1)
- Andromeda Breakthrough by Fred Hoyle and John Elliot Crest R1080 ca. 1967 (1st 1967) (Box 1)
- The A-Team by Charles Heath [Ron Renauld] Dell 10009 ca. 1984 (1st) (Box 1)
- The A-Team 2: Small But Deadly Wars by Charles Heath [Ron Renauld] Dell 10020 ca. 1984 (1st) (Box 1)
- The A-Team 3: When You Comin' Back, Range Rider? by Charles Heath [Ron Renauld] Dell 10027 ca. 1984 (1st) (Box 1)
- The A-Team 4: Old Scores to Settle by Charles Heath [Ron Renauld] Dell 10034 ca. 1984 (1st) (Box 1)
- The A-Team 5: Ten Percent of Trouble by Charles Heath [Ron Renauld] Dell 10037 ca. 1984 (1st) (Box 1)
- The A-Team 6: Operation Desert Sun: The Untold Story by Charles Heath [Louis Chunovic] Dell 10039 ca. 1984 (1st) (Box 1)
- The A-Team 6: Operation Desert Sun: The Untold Story by Charles Heath [Louis Chunovic] Dell 10039 ca. 1984 (1st), (Variant Cover) (Box 1)
- Adam-12: The Runaway by Chris Stratton [Richard Hubbard] Award AN1002 ca. 1972 (1st) (Box 1)
- Adam-12: Dead On Arrival by Chris Stratton [Richard Hubbard] Award AN1027 ca. 1972 (1st) (Box 1)
- Adam-12: The Hostages by Chris Stratton [Richard Hubbard] Award AN1174 ca. 1974 (1st) (Box 1)
- Adam-12 #4: The Sniper by Michael Stratton [Bruce Cassidy] Award AN1266 ca. 1974 (1st) (Box 1)
- The Addams Family: Drawn and Quartered by Chas Addams Pocket 50058 ca. 1941,42 (1st: 1964) (Box 1)
- The Addams Family: Black Maria by Chas Addams Pocket 50059 ca. 1960 (1st: 1964) (Box 1)
- The Addams Family: Nightcrawlers by Chas Addams Pocket 50060 ca. 1957 (1st: 1964) (Box 1)
- The Addams Family: Monster Rally by Chas Addams Pocket 50061 ca. 1950 (1st 1965) (Box 1)
- The Addams Family: Homebodies by Chas Addams Pocket 50062 ca. 1954 (1st: 1965) (Box 1)
- The Addams Family: Addams and Evil by Chas Addams Pocket 50063 ca. 1940+ (1st: 1965) (Box 1)
- The Addams Family: Dear Dead Days: A Family Album by Chas Addams Berkley F1175 ca. 1959 (1st: 1966) (Box 1)
- The Addams Family by Jack Sharkey Pyramid R-1229 ca. 1965 (1st) (Box 1)
- The Addams Family Strikes Back by W.F. Miksch Pyramid R-1257 ca. 1965 (1st) (Box 1)
- Alfred Hitchcock Presents: 12 Stories They Wouldn't Let Me Do On TV by Alfred Hitchcock, ed. Dell D231 ca. 1957 (1st: 1958) (Box 1)
- Alfred Hitchcock Presents: 13 More Stories They Wouldn't Let Me Do On TV by Alfred Hitchcock, ed. Dell D281 ca. 1957 (1st: 1959) (Box 1)
- Alfred Hitchcock Presents: Clean Crimes and Neat Murders by Henry Slesar Avon T-485 ca. 1960 (1st) (Box 1)
- Alfred Hitchcock Introduces A Crime For Mothers and Others by Henry Slesar Avon F-121 ca. 1962 (1st) (Box 1)
- Alias Smith and Jones: Dead Ringer by Brian Fox [W.T. Ballard] Award A896S ca. 1971 (1st) (Box 1)
- Alias Smith and Jones: The Outlaw Trail by Brian Fox [W.T. Ballard] Award AS1006 ca. 1972 (1st) (Box 1)
- Alias Smith and Jones: The Outlaw Trail by Brian Fox [W.T. Ballard] Award AS1006 ca. 1972 (1st) (Variant Cover) (Box 1)
- Alias Smith and Jones: Cabin Fever by Brian Fox [W.T. Ballard] ca. 1976 (Box 1)
- Alias Smith and Jones: Apache Gold by Brian Fox [W.T. Ballard] ca. 1976 (Box 1)
- Alias Smith and Jones: Trick Shot by Brian Fox [W.T. Ballard] ca. 1976 (Box 1)
- The Wit and Wisdom of Archie Bunker by Eugene Boe, ed. Popular Library 08194 ca. 1971 (1st) (Box 2)
- Edith Bunker's All in the Family Cookbook by Eugene Boe Popular Library 08195 ca. 1971 (1st) (Box 2)
- Archie Bunker's Family Album Popular Library 08216 ca. 1973 (1st) (Box 2)
- All in the Family by Burton Wohl Bantam Q2566 ca. 1976 (1st) (Box 2)
- God, Man and Archie Bunker by Spencer Marsh Bantam T7913 ca. 1975 (1st: 1976) (Box 2)
- TV's First Family by Louis Solomon Scholastic Book Services TK2297 ca. 1973 (1st) (Box 2)
- Agnes Nixon's All My Children Book I: Tara & Phillip by Rosemarie Santini Jove B4892 ca. 1980 (1st) (Box 2)
- Agnes Nixon's All My Children Book II: Erica by Rosemarie Santini Jove K4895 ca. 1980 (1st) (Box 2)
- Agnes Nixon's All My Children Book III: The Lovers by Rosemarie Santini Jove K4896 ca. 1981 (1st) (Box 2)
- All My Children #1/#2 [combined]: Once and Always, Book One and Two by Marcia Lawrence (#1) and Teresa Ward (#2) Pioneer 350 ca. 1987 (1st) (Box 2)
- Amazing Stories Book 1: The 4-D Funhouse by Clayton Emery and Earl Wajenberg TSR 74176 ca. 1985 (1st) (Box 2)
- Amazing Stories Book 2: Jaguar! by Morris Simon TSR 74177 ca. 1985 (1st) (Box 2)
- Amazing Stories Book 3: Portrait in Blood by Mark Kirchoff TSR 74186 ca. 1985 (1st) (Box 2)
- Amazing Stories Book 4: Nightmare University by Gene DeWeese and Robert Coulson TSR 74817 ca. 1975,85 (1st: 1985) (Box 2)
- Amazing Stories Book 5: Starskimmer by John Gregory Betancourt TSR 74353 ca. 1986 (1st) (Box 2)
- Amazing Stories Book 6: Day of the Mayfly by Lee Enderlin TSR 74352 ca. 1986 (1st) (Box 2)
- Steven Spielberg's Amazing Stories by Steven Bauer Charter 01906 ca. 1986 (1st) (Box 2)
- Steven Spielberg's Amazing Stories Volume !! by Steven Bauer Charter 01912 ca. 1986 (1st) (Box 2)
- American Bandstand: Your Happiest Years by Dick Clark Cardinal GC-96 ca. 1959 (1st: 1961) (Box 2)
- The Americans by Donald Honig Popular Library PC 1006 ca. 1961 (1st) (Box 2)
- An American Family by Ron Goulart Warner 78-077 ca. 1973 (Box 2)
- Anna and the King of Siam by Margaret Landon Pocket 77653 ca. 1943,44 (19th: 1972) (Box 2)
- Anna and the King of Siam by Margaret Landon Pocket 77653 ca. 1943,44 (20th: 1972) (Variant Cover) (Box 2)
- Another World by Kate Lowe Kerrigan [Frances Rickett] Ballantine 25859 ca. 1978 (1st) (Box 2)
- Another World II by Kate Lowe Kerrigan [Frances Rickett] Ballantine 25860 ca. 1978 (1st) (Box 2)
- Another World II by Kate Lowe Kerrigan [Frances Rickett] Ballantine 25860 ca. 1978 (1st) (Variant Cover) (Box 3)
- Another World #1: Let's Love Again by Edwina Franklin Pioneer 31 ca. 1986 (1st) (Box 3)
- Another World #2: Love's Destiny by Martha Winslow [Frances Rickett] Pioneer 32 ca. 1986 (1st) (Box 3)
- Another World #3: Affairs of the Moment by Martha Winslow [Frances Rickett] Pioneer 33 ca. 1986 (1st) (Box 3)
- Another World #4: Love's Encore by Martha Winslow [Frances Rickett] Pioneer 34 ca. 1986 (1st) (Box 3)
- Another World #5: Caress From the Past by Martha Winslow [Frances Rickett] Pioneer 35 ca. 1986 (1st) (Box 3)
- Another World #6: Forgive and Forget by Virginia Grace Pioneer 36 ca. 1986 (1st) (Box 3)
- Another World #7: Tangled Web by Marlene Creed Pioneer 37 ca. 1986 (1st) (Box 3)
- Another World #8: Haunted by the Past by Cordelia Burke Pioneer 38 ca. 1986 (1st) (Box 3)
- Another World #9: Suspicions by Dylan Malloy Pioneer 39 ca. 1986 (1st) (Box 3)
- Another World #10: Deceptions by Martha Winslow [Frances Rickett] Pioneer 40 ca. 1987 (1st) (Box 3)
- Another World #11: Whispers From the Past by Chloe Seid Pioneer 050 ca. 1987 (1st) (Box 3)
- Another World #12: Love Play by Amanda Perkins Pioneer 051 ca. 1987 (1st) (Box 3)
- Another World #13: Schemes and Dreams by Cordelia Burke Pioneer 052 ca. 1987 (1st) (Box 3)
- Another World #14: The Art of Love by Amanda Perkins Pioneer 053 ca. 1987 (1st) (Box 3)
- Apple's Way by Robert Weverka Bantam 9848 ca. 1975 (1st) (Box 3)
- Apple's Way by Robert Weverka Bantam N6317 ca. 1975 (2nd) (Variant Cover) (Box 3)
- The Aquanauts by Daniel Bard Popular Library G516 ca. 1961 (1st) (Box 3)
- Arrest and Trial by Norman Daniels Lancer 72-696 ca. 1963 (1st) (Box 3)
- Arrest and Trial: The Missing Witness by Norman Daniels Lancer 72-723 ca. 1964 (1st) (Box 3)
- Kids Say the Darndest Things! by Art Linkletter Cardinal C-330 ca. 1957 (1st: 1959) (Box 3)
- The Secret World of Kids by Art Linkletter Cardinal GC-92 ca. 1959 (1st: 1960) (Box 3)
- Confessions of a Happy Man by Art Linkletter Cardinal GC-124 ca. 1960 (1st: 1962) (Box 3)
- Kids Sure Right Funny! by Art Linkletter Crest k646 ca. 1962 (1st: 1963) (Box 3)
- Kids Sure Right Funny! by Art Linkletter Crest k997 ca. 1962 (unsp: 1965) (Box 3)
- A Child's Garden of Misinformation by Art Linkletter Crest d949 ca. 1965 (1st: 1966) (Box 3)
- Oops! Or, Life's Awful Moments by Art Linkletter Pocket 75179 ca. 1967 (1st: 1968) (Box 3)
- Kids Say the Darndest Things! by Art Linkletter Pocket 75278 ca. 1957 (25th: 1968) (Box 3)
- I Wish I'd Said That! by Art Linkletter Pocket 75430 ca. 1961 (3rd: 1968) (Box 4)
- Kids Still Say the Darndest Things! by Art Linkletter Pocket 75430 ca. 1961 (3rd: 1968) (Box 4)
- My Husband, Arthur Murray by Kathryn Murray with Betty Hannah Hoffman Avon T510 ca. 1959,60 (1st: 1960) (Box 4)
- As the World Turns #1: Magic of Love by Bob Bancroft Pioneer 41 ca. 1986 (1st) (Box 4)
- As the World Turns #2: Ruling Passions by Cathy Cunningham [Chet Cunningham] Pioneer 42 ca. 1986 (1st) (Box 4)
- As the World Turns #3: Lovers Who Dare by Johanna Boyd Pioneer 43 ca. 1986 (1st) (Box 4)
- As the World Turns #3: Lovers Who Dare by Johanna Boyd Pioneer 43 ca. 1986 (1st) (2nd Copy) (Box 4)
- As the World Turns #4: Horizons of the Heart by John Boyd Pioneer 44 ca. 1986 (1st) (Box 4)
- As the World Turns #6: Love Trap by Sonni Cooper Pioneer 46 ca. 1986 (1st) (Box 4)
- As the World Turns #7: Now and Forever by Angelica Aimes [Lita Scott] Pioneer 47 ca. 1986 (1st) (Box 4)
- As the World Turns #8: Shared Moments by Angelica Aimes [Lita Scott] Pioneer 48 ca. 1986 (1st) (Box 4)
- As the World Turns #9: In the Name of Love by Kacia Bennett Pioneer 49 ca. 1987 (1st) (Box 4)
- As the World Turns #10: This Precious Moment by Kacia Bennett Pioneer 50 ca. 1987 (1st) (Box 4)
- As the World Turns #11: Full Circle by Margaret Brownley Pioneer 000 ca. 1987 (1st) (Box 4)
- As the World Turns #12: Storm Warnings by Margaret Brownley Pioneer 001 ca. 1987 (1st) (Box 4)
- As the World Turns #13: The Second Time Around by Angelica Aimes [Lita Scott] Pioneer 002 ca. 1987 (1st) (Box 4)
- As the World Turns #14: Always and Forever by Kacia Bennett Pioneer 003 ca. 1987 (1st) (Box 4)
- The Asphalt Jungle by W.R. Burnett Pocket 6078 ca. 1949 (3rd: 1961) (Box 4)
- The Asphalt Jungle by W.R. Burnett Pocket 6078 ca. 1949 (3rd: 1961) (Variant Cover) (Box 4)
- The Associates by John Jay Osborn, Jr. Popular Library 04530 ca. 1979 (1st) (Box 4)
- The Avengers #1: "The Floating Game" John Garforth Brekley F1410 ca. 1967 (1st) (Box 4)
- The Avengers #1: "The Floating Game" John Garforth Brekley X1666 ca. 1967 (2nd: 1969) (Variant Cover) (Box 4)
- The Avengers #2: "The Laugh Was On Lazarus" by John Garforth Berkley F1411 ca. 1967 (1st) (Box 4)
- The Avengers #3: "The Passing of Gloria Munday" by John Garforth Berkley F1431 ca. 1967 (1st) (Box 4)
- The Avengers #3: "The Passing of Gloria Munday" by John Garforth Berkley X1668 ca. 1967 (2nd: 1969) (Box 4)
- The Avengers #4: "Heil Harris!" by John Garforth Berkley F1445 ca. 1967 (1st) (Box 4)
- The Avengers #4: "Heil Harris!" by John Garforth Berkley X1669 ca. 1967 (2nd: 1969) (Box 4)
- The Avengers #5: "The Afrit Affair" by Keith Laumer Berkley X1547 ca. 1968 (1st) (Box 4)
- The Avengers #6: "The Drowned Queen" by Keith Laumer Berkley X1565 ca. 1968 (1st) (Box 4)
- The Avengers #7: "The Gold Bomb" by Keith Laumer Berkley X1592 ca. 1968 (1st) (Box 5)
- The Avengers #8: "The Magnetic Man" by Norman Daniels Berkley X1673 ca. 1968 (1st) (Box 5)
- The Avengers #9: Moon Express" by Norman Daniels Berkley X1658 ca. 1969 (1st) (Box 5)
- Banacek by Deanne Romano Bantam N7881 ca. 1973 (1st) (Box 5)
- Banyon by William Johnston Paperback Library 64-669 ca. 1971 (1st) (Box 5)
- Banyon by William Johnston Paperback Library 74-285 ca. 1971 (2nd: 1972) (Box 5)
- Baretta: Beyond the Law by Andrew Patrick Berkley 03515 ca. 1977 (1st) (Box 5)
- Baretta: Sweet Revenge by Thom Racina Berkley 03559 ca. 1960 (1st) (Box 5)
- Bat Masterson by Richard O'Conner Bantam A1888 ca. 1957 (1st: 1958) (Box 5)
- The Bastard Photostory 1980 (Box 5)
- Batman by Bob Kane Signet D2939 ca. 1940+ (1st: 1966) (Box 5)
- Batman vs. Three Villains of Doom by Winston Lyon [William Woolfolk] Signet D2940 ca. 1966 (1st) (Box 5)
- Batman vs. The Joker by Bob Kane Signet D2969 ca. 1951+ (1st: 1966) (Box 5)
- Batman vs. The Penguin by Bob Kane Signet D2970 ca. 1952+ (1st: 1966) (Box 5)
- Funniest Fan Letters to Batman by Bill Adler, ed. Signet D2980 ca. 1966 (1st) (Box 5)
- Batman vs. The Fearsome Foursome by Winston Lyon [William Woolfolk] Signet D2995 ca. 1966 (1st) (Box 5)
- Battlestar Galactica by Glen A. Larson and Robert Thurston Berkley 03958 ca. 1978 (1st) (Box 5)
- Battlestar Galactica: The Photostory by Richard J. Anobile Berkley 04139 ca. 1979 (1st) (Box 5)
- Battlestar Galactica 2: The Cyclone Death Machine by Glen A. Larson and Robert Thurston Berkley 04080 ca. 1979 (1st) (Box 5)
- Battlestar Galactica 3: The Tomb of Kobol by Glen A. Larson and Robert Thurston Berkley 04267 ca. 1979 (1st) (Box 5)
- Battlestar Galactica 4: The Young Warriors by Glen A. Larson and Robert Thurston Berkley 04655 ca. 1980 (1st) (Box 5)
- Battlestar Galactica 5: Galactica Discovers Earth by Glen A. Larson and Michael Resnick Berkley 04744 ca. 1980 (1st) (Box 5)
- Battlestar Galactica 6: The Living Legend by Glen A. Larson and Nicholas Yermakov Berkley 05249 ca. 1982 (1st) (Box 5)
- Battlestar Galactica 7: War of the Gods by Glen A. Larson and Nicholas Yermakov Berkley 05660 ca. 1982 (1st) (Box 5)
- Battlestar Galactica 8: Greetings From Earth by Glen A. Larson and Ron Goulart Berkley 06047 ca. 1983 (1st) (Box 5)
- Battlestar Galactica 9: Experiment in Terra by Glen A. Larson and Ron Goulart Berkley 06418 ca. 1984 (1st) (Box 5)
- Battlestar Galactica 10: The Long Patrol by Glen A. Larson and Ron Goulart Berkley 07105 ca. 1984 (1st) (Box 5)
- Battlestar Galactica 11: The Nightmare Machine by Glen A. Larson and Robert Thurston Berkley 08618 ca. 1984 (1st: 1985) (Box 5)
- Battlestar Galactica 12: "Die, Chameleon!" by Glen A. Larson and Robert Thurston Berkley 09095 ca. 1986 (1st) (Box 5)
- Battlestar Galactica 13: Apollo's War by Glen A. Larson and Robert Thurston Berkley 09476 ca. 1987 (1st) (Box 6)
- Battlestar Galactica 14: Surrender the Galactica by Glen A. Larson and Robert Thurston Ace 05104 ca. 1988 (1st) (Box 6)
- Stan Lee Presents: Battlestar Galactica by Roger McKenzie Ace Tempo Star 04876 ca. 1978 (1st) (Box 6)
- Stan Lee Presents: Battlestar Galactica Volume II by Roger McKenzie Ace Tempo Star 04877 ca. 1979 (1st) (Box 6)
- Beacon Hill by Henry Clement [Edward Fenton] Popular Library 08397 ca. 1975 (1st) (Box 6)
- Beacon Hill #2: The Colonel and Fawn by Henry Clement [Edward Fenton] Popular Library 08427 ca. 1975 (1st) (Box 6)
- Beauty and the Beast by Barbara Hambly Avon 75795 ca. 1989 (1st) (Box 6)
- Beauty and the Beast: Song of Orpheus by Barbara Hambly Avon 75798 ca. 1990 (1st) (Box 6)
- Beauty and the Beast: Masques by Rus Emerson Avon 76194 ca. 1990 (1st) (Box 6)
- Ben Casey by William Johnston Lancer 70-006 ca. 1962 (1st) (Box 6)
- Ben Casey: A Rage for Justice by Norman Daniels Lancer 70-011 ca. 1962 (1st) (Box 6)
- Ben Casey: The Strength of his Hands by Sam Elkin Lancer 70-037 ca. 1963 (1st) (Box 6)
- Ben Casey: The Fire Within by Norman Daniels Lancer 70-045 ca. 1963 (1st) (Box 6)
- Vince Edwards: A Biography of Television's "Dr. Ben Casey" by George Carpozi, Jr. Belmont L92-556 ca. 1962 (1st) (Box 6)
- The Clampetts of Beverly Hills by Jerry Fay Avon G1203 ca. 1964 (1st) (Box 6)
- The Beverly Hillbillies Book of Country Humor by Lewis R. Benton, Ph.D., ed. Dell 0553 ca. 1964 (1st) (Box 6)
- Jim Owen's Hillbilly Humor by Jim M. Owen Pocket 75623 ca. 1970 (1st) (Box 6)
- Bewitched by Al Hine Dell 0551 ca. 1965 (1st) (Box 6)
- The Bionic Woman: Welcome Home, Jamie by Eileen Lottman Berkly Z3230 ca. 1976 (1st) (Box 6)
- The Bionic Woman: Extracurricular Activities by Eileen Lottman Berkly O3326 ca. 1977 (1st) (Box 6)
- Lindsay Wagner: Superstar of The Bionic Woman by David Houston Belmont Tower 50979 ca. 1976 (1st) (Box 6)
- Baa Baa Black Sheep by Col. Gregory "Pappy" Boyington Bantam 10790 ca. 1958 (1st: 1977) (Box 6)
- The Black Sheep Squadron: Devil in the Slot by Mike Jahn Bantam 11938 ca. 1978 (1st) (Box 6)
- The Black Sheep Squadron: The Hawk Flies on Sunday by Michael Jahn Bantam 13645 ca. 1980 (1st) (Box 6)
- The Black Sheep Squadron: The Hawk Flies on Sunday by Michael Jahn Golden Apple 19746 ca. 1980 (1st: 1984) (Variant Cover) (Box 6)
- Terry Nation's Blake's 7: Their First Adventure by Trevor Hoyle Citadel Press 1103 ca. 1977 (1st: 1988) (Box 6)
- Terry Nation's Blake's 7: Scorpio Attack by Trevor Hoyle Citadel Press 1082 ca. 1981 (1st: 1988) (Box 6)
- Blondie #1 by Chic Young Signet P3710 ca. 1968 (1st) (Box 7)
- Blondie #2 by Chic Young Signet P3711 ca. 1968 (1st) (Box 7)
- The Bold Ones: The Surrogate Womb by Bruce Cassiday Manor 95260 ca. 1973 (1st) (Box 7)
- The Bold Ones: A Quality of Fear by Bruce Cassiday Manor 95296 ca. 1973 (1st) (Box 7)
- The Bold Ones: To Get Along With the Beautiful Girls by Bruce Cassiday Manor 12215 ca. 1974 (1st) (Box 7)
- Bonanza by Noel Loomis Popular Library P1000 ca. 1960 (1st) (Box 7)
- Bonanza: One Man with Courage by Thomas Thompson Media M101 ca. 1966 (1st) (Box 7)
- Bonanza #2: Black Silver by William R. Cox Media M102 ca. 1967 (1st) (Box 7)
- Bonanza #1: Winter Grass by Dean Owen [Dudley Dean McGaughy] Paperback Library 52-726 ca. 1968 (1st) (Box 7)
- Bonanza #2: Ponderosa Kill by Dean Owen [Dudley Dean McGaughy] Paperback Library 52-757 ca. 1968 (1st) (Box 7)
- Boney: The Mountains have a Secret ca. 1954 (Box 7)
- Boney: The Will of the Tribe ca. 1965 (Box 7)
- Boney: Boney Buys a Woman ca. 1959 (Box 7)
- Boney: The Lake Frome Monster ca. 1969 (Box 7)
- Boney: Boney and the Black Virgin ca. 1962 (Box 7)
- Boots and Saddles: The Story of the 5th Cavalry by Edgar Jean Bracco Berkly G-180 ca. 1958 (1st) (Box 7)
- Bracken's World #1 by Doama Winston Paperback Library 64-237 ca. 1969 (1st) (Box 7)
- Bracken's World #2: The High Country by Doama Winston Paperback Library 64-279 ca. 1970 (1st) (Box 7)
- Bracken's World #3: Sound Stage by Doama Winston Paperback Library 64-364 ca. 1970 (1st) (Box 7)
- The Brady Bunch by William Johnston Lancer 73-849 ca. 1969 (1st) (Box 7)
- The Brady Bunch #2: Showdown at the P.T.A. Coral by William Johnston Lancer 73-864 ca. 1969 (1st) (Box 7)
- The Brady Bunch #3: Count Up to Blast-Down! by William Johnston Lancer 73872 ca. 1970 (1st) (Box 7)
- The Brady Bunch #4: The Bumbler Strikes Again by William Johnston Lancer 73891 ca. 1970 (1st) (Box 7)
- The Brady Bunch #5: The Quarterback Who Came to Dinner by William Johnston Lancer 73206 ca. 1970 (1st) (Box 7)
- The Brady Bunch in "The Treasure of Mystery Island", by Jack Matcha Tiger Beat XQ2011 ca. 1972 (1st) (Box 7)
- The Brady Bunch in the New York Mystery by Jack Matcha Tiger Beat XQ2014 ca. 1972 (1st) (Box 7)
- The Brady Bunch in Adventure on the High Seas by Jack Matcha Tiger Beat XQ2017 ca. 1973 (1st) (Box 7)
- Bridget Loves Bernie by Paul Fairman Lancer 74795 ca. 1972 (1st) (Box 7)
- The Brothers Brannagan by Henry E. Helseth Signet S1973 ca. 1961 (1st) (Box 7)
- Buck Rogers in the 25th Century by Addison E Steele [Richard A. Lupoff] Dell 10843 ca. 1978 (1st) (Box 8)
- Buck Rogers #2: That Man on Beta by Addison E Steele [Richard A. Lupoff] Dell 10948 ca. 1979 (1st) (Box 8)
- Buck Rogers in the 25th Century Fotonovel Fotonovel Vol. 12 c 1979 (1st) ca. 1979 (1st) (Box 8)
- The Bugaloos and the Vile Vibes by Chris Stratton [Richard Hubbard] Curtis 07131 ca. 1971 (1st) (Box 8)
- The Bugaloos #2: Rock City Rebels by Chris Stratton [Richard Hubbard] Curtis 07132 ca. 1971 (1st) (Box 8)
- The Bugaloos #3: Benita's Platter Pollution by Chris Stratton [Richard Hubbard] Curtis 07136 ca. 1971 (1st) (Box 8)
- Burke's Law: Who Killed Beau Sparrow? by Roger Fuller [Don Tracy Perma M-4310 ca. 1964 (1st) (Box 8)
- Burke's Law: Who Killed Madcap Millicent? by Roger Fuller [Don Tracy Pocket 50030 ca. 1964 (1st) (Box 8)
- ChiPs: The Erik Estrada Scrapbook by Susan Katz Tempo 17209 ca. 1980 (1st) (Box 8)
- Cade's County by Alfred Lawrence Popular Library 08184 ca. 1972 (1st) (Box 8)
- Cagney & Lacey by Serita Deborah Stevens Del 11050 ca. 1985 (1st) (Box 8)
- Cain's Hundred by Evan Lee Heyman Popular Library PC1010 ca. 1961 (1st) (Box 8)
- Can You To This? by Panelists and Guest Stars Tempo 05365 ca. 1971 (1st) (Box 8)
- Cannon #1: Murder By Gemini by Richard Gallagher Lancer 74783 ca. 1971 (1st) (Box 8)
- Cannon #1: Murder By Gemini by Richard Gallagher Lancer 74783 ca. 1971 (unsp: 1976) (Variant Cover) (Box 8)
- Cannon #2: The Stewardess Strangler by Richard Gallagher Lancer 75260 ca. 1971 (1st) (Box 8)
- Cannon: Farewell, Little Sister by Douglas Enefer Corgi 10751 ca. 1978 (1st) (Box 8)
- Capitol #1: Unspoken Desires by Mae Miner Pioneer 91 ca. 1986 (1st) (Box 8)
- Capitol #2: Intimate Glimpses by Mae Miner Pioneer 92 ca. 1986 (1st) (Box 8)
- Capitol #3: Forbidden Tomorrows by Cathy Cunningham [Chet Cunningham] Pioneer 93 ca. 1986 (1st) (Box 8)
- Capitol #4: Passion's Masterpiece by Cathy Cunningham [Chet Cunningham] Pioneer 94 ca. 1986 (1st) (Box 8)
- Adventures of Captain David Grief by Jack London Popular Library PC300 ca. 1911+ (1st: 1957) (Box 8)
- Captain Nice by William Johnston Tempo T-155 ca. 1967 (1st) (Box 8)
- Charles in Charge by Elizabeth Faucher Scholastic Book Services 33550 ca. 1984 (1st) (Box 8)
- Charles in Charge Again by Elizabeth Faucher Scholastic Book Services 41008 ca. 1987 (1st) (Box 8)
- Charlie's Angels by Max Franklin [Richard Deming] Ballantine 25665 ca. 1977 (1st) (Box 8)
- Charlie's Angels #2: The Killing kind by Max Franklin [Richard Deming] Ballantine 25707 ca. 1977 (1st) (Box 8)
- Charlie's Angels #3: Angels on a String by Max Franklin [Richard Deming] Ballantine 25691 ca. 1977 (1st) (Box 8)
- Charlie's Angels #4: Angels in Chains by Max Franklin [Richard Deming] Ballantine 27182 ca. 1977 (1st) (Box 8)
- Charlie's Angels #5: Angels on Ice by Max Franklin [Richard Deming] Ballantine 27342 ca. 1978 (1st) (Box 8)
- Farrah: An Unauthorized Biography of Farrah Fawcett-Majors by Patricia Burstein Signet W7723 ca. 1977 (1st) (Box 8)
- Farrah & Lee by Connie Berman Tempo 14275 ca. 1977 (1st) (Box 9)
- Peter Travers' Favorite TV Angels by Peter Travers Xerox N 104 ca. 1978 (1st) (Box 9)
- Chase by Norman Daniels Berkly 02553 ca. 1974 (1st) (Box 9)
- Chico and the Man: The Freddie Prinze Story by Maria Pruetzel and John A. Barbour Master's Press 89251 ca. 1978 (1st) (Box 9)
- Cimmaron Strip by Richard Mead [Ben Haas] Popular Library 60-2245 ca. 1967 (1st) (Box 9)
- Columbo by Alfred Lawrence Popular Library 01524 ca. 1972 (1st) (Box 9)
- Columbo #1 by Alfred Lawrence Popular Library 08382 ca. 1972 (unsp: 1975) (Variant Cover) (Box 9)
- Columbo #2: The Dean's Death by Alfred Lawrence Popular Library 00265 ca. 1975 (1st) (Box 9)
- Columbo #3: Any Old Port in a Storm by Henry Clement [Edward Fenton] Popular Library 00317 ca. 1975 (1st) (Box 9)
- Columbo #4: Dawn's Early Light by Henry Clement [Edward Fenton] Popular Library 00326 ca. 1975 (1st) (Box 9)
- Columbo #5: Murder by the Book by Lee Hays Popular Library 03109 ca. 1976 (1st) (Box 9)
- Columbo #6: A Deadly State of Mind by Lee Hays Popular Library 03118 ca. 1976 (1st) (Box 9)
- Combat by Harold Calin Lancer 70-042 ca. 1963 (1st) (Box 9)